[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community
So we're decreasing the font and
首先减小字体大小
we're gonna train a basic model on this data set.
我们要在这个数据中训练出一个基础模型
So the first thing I am going to do is not use the pictures but
我要做的第一件事并不是使用图片
just use the pixels of the images and
而是使用图片的像素
train a classifier on the pixels of the images and see how well that does.
并且在图片的像素基础上训练分类器 然后观察分类器的效果如何
So let's just go ahead and do it.
让我们开始吧
So #Train a classifier.
标题是 训练分类器
I misspelled it here.
抱歉我拼错了
So #Train a classifier on
恩这次写对了
the raw image pixels.
在像素基础上训练分类器
So these are going to be my features, the raw image pixels, not those deep features.
原始的照片像素就是我的特征 并不是那些深度特征
And so I'm going to call this the raw, sorry,
所以我就把这个叫做
raw_pixel_model.
原始像素模型raw_pixel_model
And the classifier I'm gonna use, I could use any classifier.
我可以用任意的分类器
The performance would be about the same.
预测结果大概差不多
I'm gonna use logistic regression,
所以我就用逻辑斯提回归了
which is what we use also in the sentiment analysis notebook.
我们在情感分析中用过
And so in logistic regression, we're gonna give it a data set.
对于逻辑斯蒂回归 在一个数据集中
So this is gonna be the training data set.
用训练数据
This is my image_train.
也就是我的image_train
I'm going to tell it what the target is.
我会告诉它目标是什么
So the target is a column in this data set called label.
目标会是数据集中叫做label标签的那一列
And that column has the label for each image.
那一列每一张图都有标签
And I'm going to tell it what features to use.
我会告诉模型 哪些特征会用到
So in this case, the features are a column called image_array.
这些特征叫做image_array
And so I'm gonna run this.
我要运行模型了
Wait, I must misspell, module, oh yes,
我又笔误了
I forgot one thing and you should have reminded me.
我在这边忘记了添加create 你们该提醒我的
In GraphLab Create, the verb that you do to create the model is create.
在GraphLab中 create这个代码代表着创造模型
So GraphLab the logistic regression,
所以正确的代码
logistic_classifier.create creates that classifier.
应该是logistic_classifier.create
So now, it should execute.
这样应该就能运行了
So we're using the raw image pixels to build a classifier.
我们用原始的照片像素来建立起了分类器
And just as a quick review, I don't expect that to be very good.
这只是快速的复习 我不期待这个预测结果能有多好
But let's go ahead and do it.
但是先做做看吧
It just is done, right now.
完成了
So let's see how it performed.
来看看预测的精确度怎么样
So the first thing that I'm gonna do is just make a prediction with the model.
第一件事是 我准备先用这个模型做预测
So let's #Make a prediction with
所以标题是用简单的像素模型预测
the simple model based on raw pixels.
#Make a prediction with the simple model based on raw pixels
So I'm gonna take some images from the test data set, and
然后我准备从测试数据集中选取一些图片
I'm gonna see what the classifier says they are.
看一下分类器的结果
So I'm gonna say image_test, and let's look at the first three images.
所以我就准备用前三张图了
So images 0:3 goes images 0, 1, and 2.
所以说images[0:3] 前三张图片
And I'm just gonna look at those images.
看一下这几张图
And I'm gonna type .show() on them just to show you what those images are.
然后我要输入type.show() 来给你看一下那几张图是什么
So here we are.
看这里就是这个
The images, as I said, are a little bit small on the data set.
图片在这个数据中有点小
But I'm gonna make this bigger so you can see, the images here are a cat,
所以我准备放大一下 你可以看到这几张图片是猫
a car, and another cat.
一辆车 和 一个猫
So two cats and a car.
所以说一共是两只猫一辆车
Car, cat, no.
车 猫 不搞错了
Cat, car, cat.
猫 车 猫
And so, I'm just gonna leave the font big so we can actually see the results.
所以我就准备把字体变得这么大 这样就能看清楚图片了
So now, let's look at the labels for this image.
看看标签吧
So this is the test data.
这是测试数据
And this is elements 0 through 3, so the first one, three.
前三个对象 所以说第一个和第三个
I visually said it was cat, car, cat, but let's see what the actual labels are.
我肉眼看到的应该是猫车猫
So, the label column and you'll see it is cat, automobile, cat.
看看原本的标签 猫 机动车 猫
So it's automobile, not car, but same thing.
它说了机动车 不是汽车 但是没什么区别了
Okay so let's see what this
所以说
raw_pixel_model predicts.
让我们来看模型预测的结果
So let me see what it predicts for this data set of three images.
让我们做个预测
So the image_test of 0:3.
所以说预测的是image_test[0:3]
So the truth is cat, automobile, cat and it predicts bird, cat, bird.
事实是猫车猫 而预测的是 鸟 猫 鸟
So it gets all three wrong, thinks the cat is a bird,
全错 它觉得猫是鸟
it thinks that car is a cat and thinks the other cat is also bird.
汽车是猫 认为第三只猫也是鸟
So, it got all wrong, but this is only kind of a fluke qualitative thing.
前三个全错了 但也可能是侥幸的结果
It could be that just the first few images it got wrong, so
可能只是前几个有错
let's take a look at what the actual predictions are.
所以看看全部的结果吧
So, let's evaluate the model of the test data and
让我们看看整个测试集模型的结果
see what the actual classification accuracy is.
和预测正确率是多少
So, #Evaluating raw pixel model on test data.
标题是衡量预测结果
So I'm going to take this raw_pixel_model and
然后用raw_pixel_model.evaluate
I'm going to call evaluate, and
用evaluate这个函数
what evaluate does is it just goes and
evaluate这个函数
computes some of those errors, those error metrics,
是用来计算失败的 那些误差矩阵
and I'm gonna use the test set.
所以我会用到测试集
And here you see the accuracy is only 46.8%.
你可以看到准确率只有在46.8%
It's terrible.
非常糟糕
You have four classes, random guess is 25%, they're balanced.
一共4类 随机猜测的正确率在25%
Here it gets 46%, not that exciting.
我们的分类器正确率只有在46% 情况不乐观
So there's more details there.
还有更多细节
The confusion matrix gets plotted.
当我们画出混淆矩阵
I'm not gonna go through that, but at home you can explore those a little bit more.
我就先不画了 你在家记得要画出来看一下
But just remember 46%.
反正记住准确率只有在46%左右
[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community